{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What do the letters NBA stand for?",
            "options": ["National Baseball Association", "National Basketball Association", "National Boxing Association", "National Bowling Association"],
            "answer": "National Basketball Association"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who has scored the most points in NBA history?",
            "options": ["LeBron James", "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar", "Kobe Bryant", "Michael Jordan"],
            "answer": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"
        },
        {
            "question": "What are the full names of the two teams in New York City?",
            "options": ["New York Knicks & Brooklyn Bulls", "New York Giants & Brooklyn Dodgers", "New York Jets & Brooklyn Nets", "New York Knickerbockers & Brooklyn Nets"],
            "answer": "New York Knickerbockers & Brooklyn Nets"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many fouls can a player commit before being ejected?",
            "options": ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
            "answer": "6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which teamâ€™s logo is shaped like a musical note?",
            "options": ["Los Angeles Lakers", "Utah Jazz", "Golden State Warriors", "New Orleans Pelicans"],
            "answer": "Utah Jazz"
        },
        {
            "question": "What team plays in Washington?",
            "options": ["Washington Wizards", "Washington Capitals", "Washington Nationals", "Washington Redskins"],
            "answer": "Washington Wizards"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many NBA teams are there today?",
            "options": ["28", "29", "30", "31"],
            "answer": "30"
        },
        {
            "question": "How long are NBA quarters?",
            "options": ["10 minutes", "12 minutes", "15 minutes", "20 minutes"],
            "answer": "12 minutes"
        },
        {
            "question": "What are the most points a player has scored in an NBA game?",
            "options": ["81 (Kobe Bryant)", "90 (Wilt Chamberlain)", "100 (Wilt Chamberlain)", "110 (Karl Malone)"],
            "answer": "100 (Wilt Chamberlain)"
        },
        {
            "question": "What Canadian cities have ever had an NBA team?",
            "options": ["Toronto (Raptors) only", "Vancouver (Grizzlies) only", "Montreal and Toronto", "Toronto (Raptors) and Vancouver (Grizzlies)"],
            "answer": "Toronto (Raptors) and Vancouver (Grizzlies)"
        }
    ]
}
